George, would you mind taking care of this for me?
George, 请帮我处理这件事好吗?
You did such a good job last time.
上次你做的很好.
Sure. I'll do it as soon as I can.
当然. 我会尽快做的.
Thanks ever so much. See you later.
太感谢了. 回头见
Bye.
George?
Yeah?
What was that all about?
这是怎么回事儿?
Oh! Sharon just wants me to arrange some transportation for a guest.
Oh! Sharon想让我为一位客人安排一下车.
Ah, that's not your job.
Ah, 那不是你的工作.
She just wants me to help her occasionally.
她只是偶尔让我帮她.
She wants you to help her occasionally?
她偶尔让你帮她?
Well...
George, I don't think so.
George, 我不这么认为.
I need you 100% in this office.
我需要你完完全全地做这间办公室里的工作.
Right.
Next time, would you please tell her that you have your own work to do?
下次, 请你告诉她你有你自己的工作要做,好吗?
I'd better do that now.
我最好现在就告诉她.
But it won't be easy coming up against her southern charm.
但她这个南方人的魅力实在是不太容易抗拒
George, why don't you just use that northern charm of yours?
George, 那你为什么不用一用你北方人的魅力呢?